Guide to the Department of Athletics, Yale University, Records Documenting Track and Cross Country
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Men's and women's track and cross country records, 1886-1997; Accession 2006-A-240
  - Track
    - General, 1886-1929 (Box 6, Folder 392)
      - NCAA, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 468)
      - NCAA-AAU, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 469)
      - New Haven, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 470)
      - NYAC, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 471)
      - NYAC (Outdoor), 1965 (Box 6, Folder 472)
      - Oxford-Cambridge, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 473)
      - Penn Relays, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 474)
      - Penn-Brown, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 475)
      - Philadelphia Inquirer Games, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 476)
      - Practice Meet, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 477)
      - Princeton, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 478 - 479)
      - St. John"s-Rutgers, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 480)
      - Opponents" Results, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 481)
      - Schedule (Outdoor), 1965 (Box 6, Folder 482)
      - Track Advisory, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 483)
      - Memos, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 484)
      - Notices, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 485)
      - Harvard (Indoors), 1966 (Box 6, Folder 486)
      - Harvard (Trip), 1966 (Box 6, Folder 487)
      - NYAC, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 488)
      - NYAC (Outdoor), 1966 (Box 6, Folder 489)
      - NY Knights of Columbus, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 490)
      - Penn Relays, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 491)
      - Penn-Brown, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 492)
      - Practice Meet, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 493)
      - Princeton (Outdoors), 1966 (Box 8, Folder 494)
      - Quantico Relays, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 495)
      - Queens-Iona Relays, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 496)
      - St. John"s-Rutgers, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 497)
      - Opponents" Results, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 498)
      - Schedule (Indoor), 1966 (Box 8, Folder 499)
      - Tartan, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 500)
      - General, 1968-1972 (Box 8, Folder 501)
      - AAU (Outdoor), 1969 (Box 8, Folder 502)
      - Army (Outdoor), 1969 (Box 8, Folder 503)
      - Boston College Relays, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 504)
      - Florida, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 505)
      - Florida Relays, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 506)
      - Harvard (Outdoor), 1969 (Box 8, Folder 507)
      - Heps (Outdoor), 1969 (Box 8, Folder 508)
      - Holy Cross Practice, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 509)
      - IC4A (Outdoor), 1969 (Box 8, Folder 510)
      - NCAA (Outdoor), 1969 (Box 8, Folder 511)
      - Piedmont Relays, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 512)
      - Penn Relays, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 513)
      - Princeton, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 514)
      - Rutgers-St. John"s, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 515)
      - South Carolina, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 516)
      - Outdoor Performances, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 517)
      - Spring Trip, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 518)
      - Army, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 519)
      - Boston College Relays, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 520)
      - Columbia-CCSU, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 521)
      - Cornell (Indoor), 1970 (Box 8, Folder 522)
      - Dartmouth, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 523)
      - Florida, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 524)
      - Florida Relays, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 525)
      - Harvard (Outdoor), 1970 (Box 8, Folder 526)
      - Harvard-Princeton (Indoor), 1970 (Box 8, Folder 527)
      - Heps (Outdoor), 1970 (Box 8, Folder 528)
      - Holy Cross-CCSU (Frosh), 1970 (Box 8, Folder 529)
      - IC4A (Indoor), 1970 (Box 8, Folder 530)
      - IC4A (Outdoor), 1970 (Box 8, Folder 531)
      - Millrose Games, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 532)
      - Penn Relays, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 533)
      - Piedmont Relays, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 534)
      - Princeton, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 535)
      - Rutgers-St. John's, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 536)
      - South Carolina, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 537)
      - UConn-Fordham, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 538)
      - UConn-UMass, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 539)
      - Spring Trip, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 540)
      - Indoor Track, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 541)
      - IC4A (Outdoor), 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 542)
      - General, 1970-1975 (Box 8, Folder 543)
      - Summaries, 1970-1975 (Box 8, Folder 544)
      - General, 1970, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 545)
      - Army, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 546)
      - Army (Outdoor), 1971 (Box 9, Folder 547)
      - Columbia (Indoor - Frosh), 1971 (Box 9, Folder 548)
      - Florida, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 549)
      - Florida Relays, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 550)
      - Harvard (Outdoor), 1971 (Box 9, Folder 551)
      - Heps (Outdoor), 1971 (Box 9, Folder 552)
      - IC4A (Outdoor), 1971 (Box 9, Folder 553)
      - Penn Relays, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 554)
      - Piedmont Relays, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 555)
      - Princeton (Indoor), 1971 (Box 9, Folder 556)
      - Princeton (Outdoor), 1971 (Box 9, Folder 557)
      - Queens-Iona Relays (Outdoor), 1971 (Box 9, Folder 558)
      - Rutgers-St. John"s, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 559)
      - South Carolina, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 560)
      - Spring Trip, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 561)
      - Holy Cross, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 562)
      - Army-Columbia (Outdoor), 1972 (Box 9, Folder 563)
      - Cornell (Indoor), 1972 (Box 9, Folder 564)
      - Dartmouth (Indoor), 1972 (Box 9, Folder 565)
      - Harvard (Outdoor), 1972 (Box 9, Folder 566)
      - Harvard-Princeton (Indoor), 1972 (Box 9, Folder 567)
      - Heps (Indoor), 1972 (Box 9, Folder 568)
      - Heps (Outdoor), 1972 (Box 9, Folder 569)
      - IC4A (Indoor), 1972 (Box 9, Folder 570)
      - Millrose, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 571)
      - NCAA (Indoor), 1972 (Box 9, Folder 572)
      - Penn Relays, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 573)
      - Penn-Brown (Indoor), 1972 (Box 9, Folder 574)
      - Practice Meet (Indoor), 1972 (Box 9, Folder 575)
      - Princeton (Outdoor), 1972 (Box 9, Folder 576)
      - Princeton Relays, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 577)
      - Queens-Iona Relays, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 578)
      - Rutgers (Outdoor), 1972 (Box 9, Folder 579)
      - UConn (Indoor), 1972 (Box 9, Folder 580)
      - UMass (Indoor), 1972 (Box 9, Folder 581)
      - Spring Trip, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 582)
      - Brown-Penn, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 583)
      - Cornell (Indoor), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 584)
      - Harvard-Princeton (Indoor), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 585)
      - Heps (Indoor), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 586)
      - Holy Cross-CCSU (Indoor), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 587)
      - IC4A (Indoor), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 588)
      - NCAA (Indoor), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 589)
      - Princeton Relays (Indoor), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 590)
      - Results, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 591)
      - Indoor, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 592)
      - Indoor, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 593)
      - Indoor, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 594)
    - Men"s and Women"s Records
      - Post Season (Men), 1979 (Box 9, Folder 595)
      - Post Season (Women), 1979 (Box 9, Folder 596)
      - General (Men), 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 597 - 599)
      - General (Women), 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 600)
      - Women"s Track Head Coach, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 601)
      - Coxe Cage Renovation Correspondence, 1979-1984 (Box 9, Folder 602)
      - Trainer"s Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 603)
      - Budget and Expenses, 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 604)
      - Results, 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 605)
      - Correspondence, 1980-1985 (Box 9, Folder 606)
      - Memos, 1980-1985 (Box 10, Folder 607)
      - Records, 1980-1989 (Box 10, Folder 608)
      - Itineraries, 1981-1989 (Box 10, Folder 609)
      - General, 1980-1989 (Box 10, Folder 610)
      - Rosters, 1981-1990 (Box 10, Folder 611)
      - Coxe Cage Renovation Ceremony Contributions, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 612)
      - Recruitment, 1982-1989 (Box 10, Folder 613)
      - Entry Forms, 1983-1989 (Box 10, Folder 614)
      - Results, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 615)
      - Budget and Expenses, 1984-1988 (Box 10, Folder 616)
      - Correspondence, 1985-1989 (Box 10, Folder 617)
      - ECAC, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 618)
      - Results, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 619)
      - Memos, 1986-1989 (Box 10, Folder 620)
      - Results, 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 621)
      - Recruitment, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 622)
      - Budget and Expenses, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 623)
      - Entry Forms, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 624)
      - Records, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 625)
      - Results, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 626)
      - Itineraries, 1990-1993 (Box 11, Folder 627)
      - Memos, 1990-1993 (Box 11, Folder 628)
      - General, 1990-1994 (Box 11, Folder 629)
      - Rosters, 1990-1994 (Box 11, Folder 630)
      - Correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box 11, Folder 631)
      - Recruitment, 1991-1993 (Box 11, Folder 632)
      - Results, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 633)
      - General, undated (Box 11, Folder 634)
  - Publications
    - Men
      - 1929-1939 (Box 11, Folder 635)
      - 1940-1949 (Box 11, Folder 636)
      - 1950-1952 (Box 11, Folder 637)
      - 1953 (Box 11, Folder 638 - 639)
      - 1954 (Box 11, Folder 640)
      - 1954 (Box 12, Folder 641)
      - 1955 (Box 12, Folder 642)
      - 1956 (Box 12, Folder 643)
      - 1957 (Box 12, Folder 644)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 645)
      - 1960-1961 (Box 12, Folder 646)
      - 1962 (Box 12, Folder 647)
      - 1963-1968 (Box 12, Folder 648)
      - 1969 (Box 12, Folder 649)
      - 1970 (Box 12, Folder 650)
      - 1971 (Box 12, Folder 651)
      - 1972-1978 (Box 12, Folder 652)
      - 1985-1990 (Box 12, Folder 653)
    - Men and Women
      - 1979-1987 (Box 12, Folder 654)
      - 1982-1997 (Box 12, Folder 655)
    - Women
      - 1981-1994 (Box 12, Folder 656)